{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_19_6Q9JQW",
                "player_16_6Q9JQW",
                "player_4_6Q9JQW",
                "player_2_6Q9JQW",
                "player_15_6Q9JQW",
                "player_6_6Q9JQW"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                19,
                16,
                4,
                2,
                15,
                6
            ],
            "animation": [
                "crouch",
                "liedown",
                "crouch",
                "stand",
                "stand",
                "pick_up"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A man with dark skin, wearing a black turtleneck, pants, and shoes.",
                "A man with dark skin, wearing a black fedora, black turtleneck, black pants, and black shoes.",
                "A woman with fair skin, wearing a white and blue shirt, blue pants, dark boots, a gray bandana, and a utility belt with pouches",
                "A woman with short dark hair, light skin, wearing a green shirt, grey cargo pants, dark gloves, and brown shoes.",
                "A bald man with medium skin, wearing a brown turtleneck, dark pants, and brown shoes.",
                "A female soldier with light skin, wearing a black beanie, tactical vest, black shirt, pants, and boots, with a white scarf and communication gear."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    -1712.134,
                    -87.529,
                    98.15,
                    0,
                    16.8124612688776,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -1345.452,
                    184.819,
                    98.15,
                    0,
                    159.01527974526255,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -1143.688,
                    118.433,
                    98.15,
                    0,
                    -21.635874025589118,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -895.242,
                    -632.115,
                    98.15,
                    0,
                    -27.81147750233916,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -892.265,
                    305.118,
                    98.355,
                    0,
                    166.2551213443948,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -1077.406,
                    312.732,
                    98.275,
                    0.0,
                    -90.0,
                    0.0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        },
        "drone": {
            "name": [
                "drone_0_6Q9JQW"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                0
            ],
            "animation": [
                "none"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "Aerial drone with a black and white frame, dual rotors, and a streamlined design."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    -1191.026,
                    240.892,
                    298.15,
                    0,
                    41.34844990158629,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None"
            ]
        },
        "car": {
            "name": [
                "car_1_6Q9JQW",
                "car_3_6Q9JQW"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                1,
                3
            ],
            "animation": [
                "None",
                "None"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "White compact car with black grille, sleek design, and four doors",
                "Yellow vehicle with black stripes, modern style, compact structure"
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    -1375.482,
                    -102.251,
                    98.15,
                    0,
                    -39.56955804011457,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -2015.273,
                    -123.785,
                    98.15,
                    0,
                    -9.544070690902073,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "BP_Hatchback_child_extras_C",
                "BP_Sedan_child_extras_C"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            -1240.667,
            -59.986,
            98.15
        ],
        "sample_radius": 977.2289029861151
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player",
        "drone",
        "car"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            -2110.032,
            698.615,
            114.096,
            0,
            -39.58668094695204,
            0
        ],
        [
            -230.9,
            -133.993,
            98.15,
            0,
            171.54671174169454,
            0
        ],
        [
            -2340.445,
            -234.213,
            98.307,
            0,
            13.865577585194348,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_black_turleneck_sweater, the_man_in_fedora_hat or the_man_in_green_sweater?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_fedora_hat",
                    "B. the_man_in_green_sweater"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_fedora_hat"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_black_turleneck_sweater, White_Compact_Car or the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. White_Compact_Car",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "A. White_Compact_Car"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_fedora_hat, the_man_in_black_turleneck_sweater or the_woman_in_floral_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_black_turleneck_sweater",
                    "B. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_camo_vest, the_man_in_green_sweater or the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_green_sweater",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_floral_shirt, the_man_in_fedora_hat or the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_fedora_hat",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_fedora_hat"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_floral_shirt, the_man_in_green_sweater or White_Drone?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_green_sweater",
                    "B. White_Drone"
                ],
                "answer": "B. White_Drone"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_woman_in_floral_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants, the_man_in_fedora_hat or White_Drone?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_fedora_hat",
                    "B. White_Drone"
                ],
                "answer": "B. White_Drone"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many people are in a crouch position?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many men are in the scene?",
                "answer": "four"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many individuals in the scene are bald?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many people are not wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "five"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many people have black skin color?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "How many cars are present in the scene?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "How many drones are present in the scene?",
                "answer": "one"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the black turtleneck sweater?",
                "options": [
                    "A. crouch",
                    "B. stand",
                    "C. lying down",
                    "D. sitting"
                ],
                "answer": "A. crouch"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the fedora hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. crouching",
                    "C. holding something",
                    "D. lying down"
                ],
                "answer": "D. lying down"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. holding something",
                    "D. walk"
                ],
                "answer": "B. crouch"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the green sweater?",
                "options": [
                    "A. crouch",
                    "B. sit",
                    "C. stand",
                    "D. run"
                ],
                "answer": "C. stand"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "What's the state of the bald man?",
                "options": [
                    "A. lying down",
                    "B. sitting",
                    "C. stand",
                    "D. crouching"
                ],
                "answer": "C. stand"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. holding something",
                    "B. sitting",
                    "C. walking",
                    "D. running"
                ],
                "answer": "A. holding something"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in floral shirt relative to the the_man_in_black_turleneck_sweater?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. In front of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the Yellow_Car relative to the the_man_in_black_turleneck_sweater?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Behind"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the the_man_in_black_turleneck_sweater relative to the the_woman_in_floral_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Behind"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the the_man_in_green_sweater relative to the the_woman_in_floral_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the the_woman_in_floral_shirt relative to the the_man_in_green_sweater?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "D. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the White_Compact_Car relative to the the_man_in_green_sweater?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-left of",
                    "B. To the back-right of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-right of"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Where is the the_man_in_green_sweater relative to the the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Where is the the_woman_in_black_vest relative to the White_Compact_Car?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "D. To the right of"
            }
        }
    }
}